that's it for you Mm For you cheer up
these gray days Yes, thank you, thank you
much appreciated What happens now So
now I'm very glad it was me
who backed the bb bag and not you Yeah
it's the bb bag Yes it's the bb bag and
given that you agree so shall
I guess what is in eh one
water bottle okay Yes, but that's because
that you see it yes points Yes you got points
Yes toothbrush Yes yes yes hygiene items
energy on filling chocolate or candy
or something of that type the most important
snacks bag comfortable clothes and slippers
so it's nice to go in and be in
So have you had children before or
slippers I haven't given birth myself but
I have been involved in two
childbirths
clothes eh charger to
electronic equipment such as toad mobile